[The seeker passes by BAILEY]
[TARZZAN]
I found you, TARZZAN!
[TARZZAN's scream]
What's that sound?
Did someone get caught?
Oh no, TARZZAN is screaming
He's screaming
That's TARZZAN
[TARZZAN is off to prison]
[BAILEY left alone after TARZZAN got caught]
Oh my god
Wow
This is...
I thought it was an actual ghost
[If you can't get out of prison within 20 minutes, you won't be able to leave until the game is over]
[Phone notification sound]
What's this?
[A member has been imprisoned]
-TARZZAN!
-A member, I think it's TARZZAN
They must've been imprisoned
I need to go save them
but
I have to stay hidden here
[Basement has no service]
[Got no text]
Oh my goodness...
Should I be staying here?
[No service area]
[The seeker is currently on the second floor]
[ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
-Should we go save TARZZAN or not?
Let's take a break together
and just survive until the end
Okay
TARZZAN is probably getting enough airtime
-while he's alone in prison
-Yeah
I feel like he'll be working out and stuff
You're right
This is killing me
Oh no, I went down to the basement
to rescue BAILEY
I had no idea the seeker would catch me
Is it possible
to break out of prison?
This is right up my alley
so if we can break out...
As long as my head can fit,
I can break out
[Members' phone numbers]
-Hold up
I have their phone numbers
[If you can't escape prison within 20 minutes,
you won't be able to leave until the game is over]
-Okay, first of all...
[ANNIE, Seeker, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
TARZZAN
-take a good break over there
-They're coming
Be quiet
The seeker is here
[ANNIE, Seeker, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
[Phone notification sound]
I turned it off
How do you turn it off?
Hello?
WOOCHAN?
He's not picking up
That's so cruel
[WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO]
[The Seeker heard the phone ring]
[Enters the room]
The Seeker is here
[WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO]
[There's only a wall between these two and the seeker]
[Seeker]
[Seeker wandering around the balcony]
[Turns around and leaves the room]
Wow, it just passed by us
It left?
[Sound of WOOCHAN's sigh]
[Sound of the seeker]
[ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
Someone is moving, right?
Who's that over there?
[Seeker, ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
[ANNIE]
It's coming this way
[Seeker getting closer to ANNIE]
I'm terrified, what do I do?
[ANNIE, Seeker, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
It's out there! I can see it.
[Already right in front of her]
[ANNIE]
I found you, ANNIE!
I'll go
[ANNIE is off to prison]
What if everyone else got caught?
Aside from us?
That could be the case
But we both turned off our phones
so we wouldn't know if we got anything
Why didn't you pick up?
How am I supposed to pick up?
I've been calling you guys
but nobody is picking up
Oh, you did call
She's in the no service area though
[TARZZAN gives BAILEY a call]
[BAILEY]
[As expected, BAILEY's phone doesn't ring]
This is terrifying
[Calls WOOCHAN again]
His phone is completely off
He must've turned it off
because it was too loud
What if he doesn't know it's us?
But I have a key
-Really?
-Yeah
Excuse me...
Hey!
Are you going to escape without me?
One is better than none
Hurry and bring a key
I only have ten minutes left
until I'm stuck here forever
Hold up
[ANNIE escapes prison]
[ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
[ANNIE escapes prison
goes to the third floor]
[She goes in the fire cabinet?]
[Sound of the fire cabinet closes]
I better hide in here
There's even a fan waiting for me here
I have a fan as well
[ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
[BAILEY]
But I'm literally
terrified right now
[BAILEY on B1]
[Seeker came down to the basement]
[BAILEY and Seeker on B1]
[BAILEY]
[Seeker]
[Sound of the seeker]
[Couldn't find BAILEY and leaves]
That's scary
I'm sweating
even though I'm not moving
Yeah
Is it like,
only those that endure the pain
can win or something?
[Seeker heads up the stairs]
[Arrived on the third floor]
[Seeker] [ANNIE]
[Sound of the seeker]
[Seeker, ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
I figured out a good method
What is it?
If the seeker comes
we can just hold the door
[Seeker]
[WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO]
What if they come from up here?
Like they put their hair down like this?
[Sound of the seeker]
It's here
[ANNIE, Seeker, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
[Sound of the door closing]
I think it left
No
I found you, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO!
[WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO off to prison]
Oh, there's one person here
TARZZAN!
Hey you traitors
Why?
Do you know how many times I called you?
That was you?
We turned off our phones
We almost died because of you
I'm dead in two minutes
No, I have two keys right now
so I can save you
but do you know
what the best plan looks like right now?
-What?
-You have to stay here
in prison for as long as you can
BAILEY is alone in the basement
in the no service area, I think
Really?
Then since you don't have much time left
Let's go together
We can't
-You can go by yourself
-I'm scared
We're going to stay here
as long as possible
Hurry and save him
-Wait for now
-Save him
[Only 20 seconds left to escape]
-I have 20 seconds left
-He only has 20 seconds left, save him
We'll save TARZZAN
-No, after five seconds
-No, save him now
You have to find a key
Find a key and then go to BAILEY
[TARZZAN escapes prison with WOOCHAN's key]
-I'm begging you
Don't let my key go to waste
[TARZZAN escapes prison]
[Phone notification sound]
[Key hint, 1st floor]
[TARZZAN listens to WOOCHAN and
looks for the key]
Where's the helmet?
[Phone notification sound]
I got another message
Once you only have 2,222 seconds
of playtime left
the seeker will disappear
The seeker will disappear
and you'll be given four minutes to hide
The four minutes begin
when the hide and seek song plays
and you're unable to save members
during those four minutes
After the four minutes,
there'll be two seekers, so hide better
There's going to be two seekers?
Yeah
Hold on! We're reaching 2,222 seconds
[Alarming them that it's 2,222 seconds ]
Sheesh
[Seeker is gone for four minutes]
[Only ALLDAY PROJECT is left here]
[Time left until the seeker is back]
[Rustling]
I'm going to use this paper
[Going to block the door with paper]
There we go!
[Tries to cover it up so she won't get caught even if someone
opens the fire cabinet]
Okay
I'll tape that there
This is why people need to learn
how to use tools
[But the paper keeps sliding down]
It's fine ANNIE, stay calm
You can do it
[Time left until the seeker is back]
[Trap]
-Has it been 2,222 seconds?
-It has
You can leave!
-Use your key
-Oh, I'll use my key
WOOCHAN is going to use a key
Is this the right thing to do?
You want to waste more time here?
Yeah
It's too late though
-Okay
-You go to the place with the helmet and find the key
Keep this with you
Thank you
[Handkerchief from WOOCHAN]
-Then I'll use this
and how should I spend
this time alone?
Am I dead in nine minutes?
[Will WOOCHAN be able to save
YOUNGSEO within nine minutes]
-WOOCHAN! I only have nine minutes left!
He probably heard me, right?
Okay, let's go to the helmet
[TARZZAN]
[Time left until the seeker is back]
[WOOCHAN]
-I'm back
-Huh? Okay
There's no seeker for four minutes
For four minutes? Okay
[Key hint, 1st floor]
We need to find the helmet
within the four minutes
It's over here!
-Hey!
-It's slippery
I'm totally carrying the group
I'm carrying the group..
That's not it, I'm sorry
It has two helmets
[Key hint, 1st floor]
[Right behind them but didn't see]
Let's check the basement!
-It does say it's on the first floor
-Does it?
[TARZZAN and WOOCHAN end up looking at the wrong place]
There's supposed to be two helmets
[Time until the seeker is back]
-A helmet
-We have to find it to save YOUNGSEO
[BAILEY]
[BAILEY is still hiding in the basement]
Where are the members?
I miss them
[Meanwhile, ANNIE has completely sealed up the door]
How do I turn this off?
I have to turn this off first
Do I have to unplug this?
[Time until the seeker is back]
[ANNIE]
[ANNIE even turns off the light]
Do you think WOOCHAN found the helmet
and the key to break me out of here?
I'm dead in seven minutes
Hey...
We need to hurry up and find it
because the seekers are coming back
First of all... hey
Have you been here?
I haven't
Hey, this place
You're saying this is where BAILEY is
[BAILEY]
Save me please
We have to find a key
We will...
-but first
-It's kind of cool here
BAILEY!
TARZZAN?
[Time left until the seeker is back]
WOOCHAN?
"Ready or not"
"Here I come"
Are you still here?
I'm scared
Come here
Why, I'm scared
-Come out
-Why?
-Look for the key
-I have to look for the key
"Ready or not"
"Here I come"
-They're here now
-Hide!
Hide!
Not here
Where?
"Ready or not"
"There are two seekers"
I have to stay quiet
Are you all done hiding?
We're not!
I have to find a key
We're coming after you now
[ANNIE]
It's so hot
If you want to see how hot it is
look at this
The sweat on my shirt
is crazy right now
[Sound of the seeker]
[Seeker heads up to the third floor]
[ANNIE]
Oh no!
They must be coming close
[ANNIE]
(Lights off)
[Seeker stopped in front of the fire cabinet]
[Leaves after checking the hallway]
I think it left now
Why is this so scary?
[The other seeker is on the first floor]
[But there are no members on the first floor]
[WOOCHAN, TARZZAN and BAILEY on B1]
[Three people hiding in the basement]
[WOOCHAN moves somewhere]
TARZZAN!
Yeah
-WOOCHAN?
-WOOCHAN
-The seeker isn't here yet
-Yeah
I can't stay there because
I feel like an actual ghost is there
Yeah, let's stick together
It's scary, right?
Yes
I know a good hiding place outside
-Outside?
-Yes
I think this is a good spot
This is a good spot
Hey! Come over here!
-WOOCHAN
-WOOCHAN, come over here!
[WOOCHAN closes the door]
WOOCHAN!
Yo! TARZZAN
Yo, check this out
Can you close this door?
-Come in after you do
-Come in
Come on in. Hurry
Wait, then I'll close all the doors
[WOOCHAN closes all the cabinet doors]
They're here
Did you hear them?
Yeah, I've heard them
Wait, behind you
Come in more
[Seeker in the basement]
[Seeker, TARZZAN, BAILEY and WOOCHAN on B1]
[Members]
[Members hiding in the ventilation room
at the end of the basement]
They're coming
-Turn off the light
-Yeah, hold on
[Members]
I'm terrified right now
The seeker is here
[Seeker is right in front of the members]
[BAILEY CAM]
[It opened the cabinet?]
[Couldn't see the members since it's too dark]
[BAILEY CAM]
[Seeker]
[Members]
[Opens up the cabinet next to them too]
[But couldn't find the members and leaves]
[20 minute alarm]
I'm dead
[Been 20 minutes, YOUNGSEO is unable to escape]
-Do I just stay here now?
[YOUNGSEO is unable to escape]
[ANNIE]
[Phone notification sound]
[Key hint, B1]
They're saying there's a key there
but that's in the basement
TARZZAN better
find the one in the basement
I can't leave this spot
Sorry
[These three didn't receive the text as they get no service]
There's no service here right now
[Members]
-I don't think we can save YOUNGSEO
Yeah, I don't think we can
It's already too late
-Really?
-Yeah
I feel sorry now. I told her I was going to save her
[Two keys left]
[80% survival rate]
[Seeker is back on the third floor]
[ANNIE]
[Sound of the seeker]
[Walks past ANNIE this time as well]
[Seeker]
[ANNIE]
[ANNIE cools down for a moment]
[TARZZAN, BAILEY, WOOCHAN and Seeker on B1]
[The second Seeker is still at the basement]
[Sound of the seeker]
It's here
[Seeker]
[Checks the cabinet again]
[Members]
[Members' point of view]
[Seeker]
[Checks the cabinet with the members]
[But doesn't see them]
[And heads to a different floor]
[Sound of BAILEY's sigh]
Look, he's taking it off again
[Members]
I feel much better taking off my shirt
The game should be over soon...
When is this over?
[Seeker went up to the first floor]
[Searches high and low for the members]
[But can't seem to find them this time]
[Other seeker looking around the second floor]
[As expected, it's hard to find the hiding members]
["Seeker vs ALLDAY PROJECT" who will win?]
[Phone notification sound]
There'll be 444 seconds left soon
The shadows faster than the seeker
will spring into action
If you get caught by the shadow
they'll make a sound
to reveal your location
so ensure you don't get caught
444 seconds...
I think we can win
We all have to
turn off our phones
You don't get service down here
[No service area]
You don't get service here
They said DAY ONE can receive a present
so guys!
Hide well
[Four members caught by the seeker]
[Three of the escaped, so the current survival rate is 80%]
[Used all the keys they had]
[All that's left is 444 seconds]
[What will ALLDAY PROJECT's final survival rate be?]
[They show themselves at the 444 second mark]
[Shadows begin seeking]
[Sound of the shadows at work]
Oh no, something is here
[Makes their way to the third floor]
[ANNIE]
Hold on
[They reach for the fire cabinet?]
[A shadow checks the room right next to the fire cabinet]
[Couldn't find ANNIE in the end]
[They turn around and head to the basement]
I did hear something out there
Me too
What do we do?
[Shadows, TARZZAN, BAILEY and WOOCHAN on B1]
[Arrived in the ventilation room where
the members are hiding]
-They're here
[Shadow]
[Shadows check the cabinets]
[Sound of the shadows]
[Couldn't find anyone so turns around]
[The shadows' sounds get faint]
I'm getting tired
[Time left]
If they survive a bit longer
I think we can get gifts for DAY ONE
[100 seconds left]
[The seeker moves faster]
Don't do anything
I feel like it should be over now
[Time left]
At this point, we've basically won, right?
[Shadows come closer]
They're coming
[Members]
[Shadows are back in the ventilation room]
They're coming
[Sound of the shadows that found the members]
[Found the members in the dark]
Oh no
I found you! TARZZAN, BAILEY, and WOOCHAN!
[TARZZAN, BAILEY, WOOCHAN off to prison]
It's because you talked
Are we supposed to
stay still when the shadows are here?
They couldn't see us
-but you went "huh?" so we got caught
-Is that why?
Yeah, it's fine
Can't find you, little birdie
I guess the game is over,
I heard them
Can't find you, little birdie
[Hide and seek is over]
[Final survival rate is 20%]
[Seekers win]
[Phone notification sound]
[Hide and seek is over,
head to the prison to check the survival rate]
Did we win?
Did you not get caught?
It's over
-You all got caught?
-I'm tired
How did the three of you
all get caught at once?
The three of us
were hiding in the same spot
and that was the perfect place to hide
so we stayed there until the end
but we made a sound
when the shadows came
But why were you three together?
[ANNIE, the only survivor, joins the members]
-ANNIE
Where were you hiding?
Where the seeker originally was
Inside the fire cabinet
where the seeker was
We could've won
if we survived from the shadows
If the three of you stayed alive
for a couple seconds, we would've won
[Seeker's screech]
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six
five, four, three, two, one!
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]